findanyfilm.com 2017-07-17

# Privacy | FindAnyFilm

All Films.All Above Board.NOW INCLUDES TV SHOWS & TV LISTINGS

  1. This website (the "Find Any Film Site") is operated by Find Any Film Ltd ("Find Any Film" "we" or "us") in association with the Industry Trust for IP Awareness Ltd. We regard your privacy as important and comply with the Data Protection Act 1998. This Privacy Policy sets out our data processing practices and your options regarding the ways in which your personal information is used. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact us.
  2. ## Information collected

You are welcome to access our site without disclosing your personal data. We collect information automatically about your visit to our web site to improve our online service.  
We also collect personal information from visitors to this website through the use of online forms. We will only use any personal information you provide us for the purposes described in the website, and from time to time to supply you with information that we believe may be of interest to you, including marketing information about our activities. 
  3. ## Who is collecting your information?

When you are on the Find Any Film Site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with Find Any Film alone unless stated otherwise. 
  4. ## With whom does Find Any Film share your information?

Find Any Film will only disclose your personal information to other companies within our group of companies, business partners, government bodies and law enforcement agencies, successors in title to our business and suppliers we engage to process data on our behalf.   
We collect log file information from all our visitors to the Find Any Film Site. Log files automatically record website usage and information such as the time, date, IP address, HTTP status and bytes sent and received. We use this information to improve our online service and to make changes to the layout of the Find Any Film Site and to the information on it, based on the way visitors move around it. We use our log files to record your visit to the site on an anonymous basis if you do not provide us with log in information. If you log in to the site our log files record your name, email, postcode and your activity on the site, including your use of Buzz. 
  5. ## Access right

You can ask us whether we are keeping personal data about you by writing to Find Any Film, 3 Soho Square, London, W1D 3HD. Once we have received your request we will respond within 40 days. There is an administrative charge of £10 for this service.   
We do everything we can to keep the information we have about you accurate and up to date. If however, you find errors or inaccuracies in your data, we will erase, complete or amend that information upon request. 
  6. ## What happens when you link to another site?

The Find Any Film Site contains links to other websites which are outside of our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours. 
  7. ## Internet-based transfers

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing the Find Any Film Site and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way.
